Believing is Everything
Over the Moon is a animation, adventure, family film directed by Glen Keane.
Fueled by memories of her mother, resourceful Fei Fei builds a rocket to the moon
on a mission to prove the existence of a legendary moon goddess.
Fei Fei (voice), played by Cathy Ang.
Chang'e (voice), played by Phillipa Soo.
Chin (voice), played by Robert G. Chiu.
Gobi (voice), played by Ken Jeong.
Father (voice), played by John Cho.
Mrs. Zhong (voice), played by Sandra Oh.
Over the Moon is a 2020 animated musical fantasy film directed by Glen Keane (in his feature directorial debut) and co-directed by John
Kahrs, from a screenplay by Audrey Wells, with additional screenplay material by Alice Wu and Jennifer Yee McDevitt.
The film was produced by Pearl Studio and Netflix Animation,
and animated by Sony Pictures Imageworks.
It stars the voices of Cathy Ang, Phillipa Soo, Ken Jeong, John
Cho, Ruthie Ann Miles, Margaret Cho, and Sandra Oh.
The plot follows an adventurous girl named Fei Fei, who builds a rocket
ship to meet the mythical goddess on the Moon Chang'e.
Over the Moon was first shown at the Montclair Film Festival on October 17, 2020,
followed by its Netflix and select theaters release on October 23.
The film grossed $860,000 worldwide; it earned a Golden Globe nomination for Best Animated
Feature Film, and was nominated for Best Animated Feature at the 93rd Academy Awards.
It is the final film Wells worked on before her
death and was dedicated to her memory.
The film explores themes of moon, musical, rocket, approving.